fih.ch 2018-10-20

# Privacy | FIH

Privacy Policies

The International Hockey Federation (“FIH” or "we", “us” or “our”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This policy sets out the basis on which any personal information we collect from you will be stored and processed by us. By visiting www.fih.ch (“our Website”) you are accepting and consenting to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

 **Information collection and use**  
We may collect and process the following information about you:

  * technical information, including the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect to the Internet, browser type and version, time zone setting, operating system and platform; and
  * information about your visit to our Website, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL)
  * tracked activity relating to your receipt of the FIH email newsletter. This may include: the opening of emails, forwarding of emails, the clicking of links within the email content, times, dates and frequency of activity (this is by no means a comprehensive list).

FIH will collect personal information when you register for certain products and services on our Website, such as the FIH email newsletter, and when you enter competitions, prize draws or similar services sponsored by our Suppliers and Partners. 

If registration is required, FIH may request your name, email address, and some other personal information. Once you register with FIH and/or sign in to our products or services, the information you provide will be stored securely by FIH until such time that it is no longer required or has no use.

Knowing something about our users is necessary to ensure that our Website is continually improved. We would like to understand our users needs and wishes in order to improve our communications with you. 

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * to administer our Website and for internal research purposes;
  * to deliver and measure advertising; and
  * to provide you with information about certain goods or services that may interest you.

**Cookies**  
Our Website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our Website. Generally speaking, cookies do not contain personal information from which you can be identified, unless you have provided such information. We use cookies in order to provide you with a good experience when you browse our Website. It also allows us to improve our Website. For more information about the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them access our Cookie Policy here.

 **Disclosure of your information**  
You agree that we have the right to share your personal information with our Suppliers and Partners and any other third parties directly associated with FIH. We may also disclose your information to advertising companies that require the information to provide relevant adverts to you. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users. We may also share such aggregate information with our Suppliers and Partners. We will also disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a legal obligation to do so. 

  **Where we store your personal information**  
The information that we collect is transferred to, stored at and processed at destinations outside the European Economic Area whose laws may not extensively protect your privacy rights. You agree to your information being transferred or processed in this way.  We will use our best efforts to ensure your information is kept securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **Your rights**  
You have the right to un-subscribe to the services we provide, such as the FIH email newsletter, at any time through an automated system. This process is detailed at the footer of each email newsletter. If an automated un-subscription system is unavailable, clear instructions on how to un-subscribe will be detailed instead.

Our Website may contain links to and from the websites of our Suppliers and Partners.  These websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility for those policies.  

If you wish to receive a copy of the personal information that we hold about you, please let us know. We may charge a small fee for providing this service, simply to cover administration costs.  

 **Amendments to our Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy ensures that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and in which circumstances share it with third parties. 

COOKIE POLICY  
This Cookie Policy covers the services provided by the following websites, owned and controlled by International Hockey Federation (“FIH” or "we", “us” or “our”): 

1\. fih.ch   
2\. worldcup2018.hockey   
(“our Websites”)

 **About cookies**  
In common with many other website operators, we may use standard technology called 'cookies' on the above websites. 

Cookies are small text files containing pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive or other access device when you visit our Websites.  Depending on the services you request, or that are being made available on our Websites, the information stored in a cookie may relate to your browsing habits on our Websites, or a unique identification number so that our Websites can "remember" you on your return visit. Cookies can be read by our Websites on your subsequent visits. Generally speaking, cookies do not contain personal information from which you can be identified, unless you have offered such information to our Websites.

 **How we use cookies**  
We use cookies in order to make our Websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to FIH. 

The cookies on our Websites are used to improve services for you through, for example:

  * Measuring how many people are using services, so they can be made easier to use and there’s enough capacity to ensure they are fast;
  * Analysing anonymised data to help us understand how people interact with services provided on our Websites so that we can make our Website services better.

**What cookies we use and why we use them**

The cookies use on our Websites fall into two categories:

 **On-site cookies**  
These are our own cookies, controlled by us and used to provide information about usage of our websites. We may use on-site cookies that are necessary to deliver certain services to you – for example, to do things like save registration information, remember language selection and remember if you have voted in a poll. These cookies do not track your usage.

  **Third-party cookies**  
These are cookies found in other companies’ internet tools, which we are using to enhance our Websites. For example, we use Google Analytics to track things like the number of people that are using our Websites, where they are coming from and what content they are viewing. This information is collected for research purposes only, it does not identify any individual and FIH will provide only use aggregated data from these analyses to third parties. This helps us to measure whether we could improve areas of our Websites. We do not control the these cookies and you should check the third party websites for more information about these

 We use Google AdWords amongst other remarketing tools to advertise Hockey across the Internet. Remarketing will display relevant ads tailored to you based on what parts of the FIH website you have viewed by placing a cookie on your machine. This cookie does not in anyway identify you or give access to your computer.  The cookie is used to say “This person visited this page, so show them ads relating to that page.” Remarketing allows us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.

 **How to manage cookies**  
Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change the preferences or settings on your web browser to control and manage cookies. The procedure for changing the preferences or settings depends on the web browser that you have chosen to use. If you wish to manage cookies yourself, or stop your computer or other device accepting cookies, go to the help section of your internet browser (for example Internet Explorer or Firefox) where you will find information on how to do this. In some cases, you can choose to accept cookies from our Websites, but block them from third parties. In others, you can block cookies from specific advertisers, or clear out all cookies.  
Please note that by removing our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our Websites.
